youtring.com 2012-06-18

# Privacy Policy

  * Home
  * Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy culls out how we treat and safeguard your personal information. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website users. This Privacy Policy explains what personal data of the users are collected from this website, how we process, store, disclose and use the personal information. 

Collection of Data

We may collect, store and process the following information about the users to the website:

  * Information about your computer like IP address, geographical location, operating systems etc.
  * Information about your visits to and use of the websites like browser type and versions, website navigations etc.
  * Information regarding purchases you make from our website
  * Information you provide us when you register with us like names, email address, telephone numbers, postal address etc.
  * Any other information that may be provided by you at your sole discretion

Usage of Data

The information collected by us shall be used for the following purposes:

  * For promotional, analytical and statistical purposes.
  * For auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and websites.
  * To verify your authority
  * To contact you when reasonably necessary
  * To detect and prevent faults, breaches of our network security, the law or our contract terms
  * To comply with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm and ensuring the security of our network and websites.
  * To administer or monitor the website
  * To supply the services availed through the website
  * To send statements or invoices for the services availed
  * To collect or refund payments, as the case may be
  * To send general marketing or non marketing communications which we think may be of interest to you 
  * For any other purposes not known at present. In case, we plan to use your information for any other purposes, we shall intimate you in advance and shall take your prior consent.

An opt-out opportunity shall be provided to you when you provide any information to us. But opting out from receiving such information shall preclude you from receiving such information in future. You may also instruct us not to use your personal information for any marketing communications by email at any time.

Disclosure of information

We may disclose your personal information in the following circumstances:

  * As and when required under law or where it is obligatory to do so. 
  * If we believe it to be appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud or fraud prevention
  * In connection with any ongoing or likelihood legal proceedings in case of infringement, piracy, or for any other unlawful activity.
  * To any of our employees, officers, staff or contractors to fulfill the obligation mentioned in this policy or the terms of use.
  * In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights
  * To our contractors, processing partners etc. located outside European Economic Area 

Unless a prior written consent is provided by you, we shall not disclose, sell or share your personal information to any third party, except as provided hereinabove.

Security of Information

We shall take all precautionary measures including operational as well as technical to avoid any failure, loss or misuse of any personal data. We store all information you provide on our firewall protected secure servers. We also use SSL Technology to encrypt any transactions you enter electronically on our website. We do not guarantee the safety or security of disclosing or transferring any information online. You understand and acknowledge that disclosing or transmitting information over the internet may not be completely secure and hence will not hold us liable for any breach of security or disclosure of information.

Verifying and updating any Information

You may verify or update any information we hold about you. We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information upon your request. You may be required to make the payment of the fee as fixed by law and supply of your identity proof as evidence, to access your information. In case you feel that any information we hold about you is incorrect or needs updating, please contact us immediately and we shall ensure to update or correct the same at the earliest.

Changes to Privacy Policy

We may at our sole discretion change this Privacy Policy to show any amendment, rectification or modification. The updated Policy shall be uploaded on the website. You should regularly visit this page to ensure you are aware of the changes, if any.

Privacy Policy of Third Parties

You may be linked to third party websites, through our websites. Those linked third party websites are not under our control and may contain a different privacy policy. You are advised to read the privacy policy of those third party websites. We shall not be responsible or liable for any damages or losses suffered through your use of the linked websites.

Cookies Policy

We may use cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our websites in order to improve the quality of our websites.To view our Cookie Policy, please click here.

Consent

You automatically consent to our collection, usage and disclosure of your information by using and continuing to use this website. In case you do not agree to such collection, usage or disclosure, you may simply stop using the website. If you have any enquiry, suggestions or feedback, you may contact us at [info@phonekall.com](mailto:info@phonekall.com)
